[{"answer": "Tell my friend", "docId": "Do-The-Right-Thing.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I ain't getting shit", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Shaddup, my friend", "docId": "Do-The-Right-Thing.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "You get paid to do what we say", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Fuck dat shit.  I deliver pizzas. That's what I get paid for", "docId": "Do-The-Right-Thing.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "What we say.  I didn't hear my friend say nuthin'", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Doctor, always try to do the right thing", "docId": "Do-The-Right-Thing.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "That's it", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "If you don't make a stand, he's gonna be beating ya like a egg for the rest of your life", "docId": "Do-The-Right-Thing.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "That's what I think", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "You the man", "docId": "Do-The-Right-Thing.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "No, you the man", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Who told you to step on my sneakers? Who told you to walk on my side of the block?  Who told you to be in my neighborhood", "docId": "Do-The-Right-Thing.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Who told you to buy a brownstone on my block, in my neighborhood on my side of the street", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "How much did you pay for them", "docId": "Do-The-Right-Thing.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "A hundred bucks", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Let it be broke", "docId": "Do-The-Right-Thing.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "It's dug", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Before I get off work", "docId": "Do-The-Right-Thing.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Do I love you", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "my friend, I think secretly that you wish you were my friend.  That's what I think.  my friend, what do you say", "docId": "Do-The-Right-Thing.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I didn't know you could read", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Keep dreaming", "docId": "Do-The-Right-Thing.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Well, fuck you, too, and fuck my friend", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Can you pay me now", "docId": "Do-The-Right-Thing.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "my friend, just this once, do me that solid", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "my friend, just this once, do me that solid", "docId": "Do-The-Right-Thing.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I would like to get paid now", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I understand", "docId": "Do-The-Right-Thing.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I love you, Black", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Buggin' Out, I don't mean to be disrespectful, but you can really direct your energies in a more useful way", "docId": "Do-The-Right-Thing.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I'm down, but for a worthwhile cause", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Nice", "docId": "Do-The-Right-Thing.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Innocent", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "You should see the way he looks at you.  All my friend wants to do is hide the salami", "docId": "Do-The-Right-Thing.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "I might be, but you're not welcome here", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "One has nuthin' to do with the other", "docId": "Do-The-Right-Thing.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "I'm getting paid..", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "She's feeling it", "docId": "Do-The-Right-Thing.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "That was the last call for tonight on Mister Seor Love Daddy's Love Line.  I love you.  You I love", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "I can't be staying long anyway", "docId": "Do-The-Right-Thing.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Long enough for us to do the nasty", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "I love you", "docId": "Do-The-Right-Thing.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Good.  I want you to listen", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "my friend is not to be trusted.  No Moulan Yan can be trusted.  The first time you turn your back, boom, a knife right here.  In the back", "docId": "Do-The-Right-Thing.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "I know", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "You don't like Public Enemy?  It's the dope shit", "docId": "Do-The-Right-Thing.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "I don't like anything else", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "Ya back is got", "docId": "Do-The-Right-Thing.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "My brother", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "my friend, I'll be right back", "docId": "Do-The-Right-Thing.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "I am a man", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "I didn't", "docId": "Do-The-Right-Thing.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "We're still standing", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "Don't even ask about your money. Your money wouldn't even pay for that window you smashed", "docId": "Do-The-Right-Thing.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "You're right, a kid is dead, but my friend, this isn't the time", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "You only pay me tw", "docId": "Do-The-Right-Thing.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "You keep it", "qsentId": 58}]